MIRELIS RIVAS-SOTO

Atlanta, GA 30309 • 404-369-6639 • mirelisrivas@gmail.com • U.S. Citizen

"...it was a pleasure to be recognized on my second flight, [Mirelis] is a great addition to Delta."

- Delta Air Lines Customer

SUMMARY

Flight Attendant with nine years of experience in domestic and international commercial flights. I demonstrate exceptional customer service and represent/promote my corporation's brand exceptionally. Proficient in emergency situations, as well as diffusing situations from reaching dangerous levels.

EXPERIENCE

DELTA AIR LINES, INC.

Atlanta, GA

Flight Attendant

April 2017 - Present

- Ensure the safety and comfort of our passengers while providing exceptional customer service.
- Provide leadership and maintain order during high stress situations including distressed customers, aircraft evacuation, security threats, delays, severe weather conditions, and turbulence, etc.
- Administer and coordinate emergency procedures or provide emergency care, as needed.
- Conduct onboard sales of food, liquor, and duty-free items.

DELTA AIR LINES, INC.

Atlanta, GA

Customer Service Agent

February 2015 – April 2017

- Provide excellent customer service including seat assignments, requests and customer service at high traffic areas of the ticketing desk and at the international/domestic gates.
- Operate jet way, place in position for aircraft arrival and departure.
- Utilize computers systems such as SNAPP and Delta Term to complete guest check-in, boarding and on time departure of all assigned flights.
- Ensure passenger's PII and company's sensitive information is secured.

ENDEAVOR AIR, INC.

New York, NY

Flight Attendant Trainer

September 2014 – February 2015

- Evaluate and qualify new hire flight attendants.
- Conduct new hire flight attendant Initial Operating Experience Flight.
- Ensure all flight attendants preformed satisfactory and follow Endeavor Air and FAA guidelines while on duty.

ENDEAVOR AIR, INC.

Atlanta, GA

Flight Attendant

September 2008 – February 2014

- Ensure the safety and comfort of our passengers while providing exceptional customer service.
- Provide leadership and maintain order during high stress situations including distressed customers, aircraft evacuation, security threats, delays, severe weather conditions, and turbulence, etc.
- Administer and coordinate emergency procedures or provide emergency care, as needed.
- Conduct onboard sales of food, liquor, and duty-free items.
- CRJ 200/900 qualified. Ability to work as a single crewmember

EDUCATION

INTERAMERICAN UNIVERSITY OF PUERTO RICO

Aguadilla, PR

Associate of Science in Computer Science - Dean's List

Fall 2013 - Spring 2016

SKILLS/INTERESTS

Bilingual: Possess excellent oral/written communication skills in English and Spanish

FAA Certs: Certificate of Demonstrated Proficiency

Equipment: Airbus 319, 320, 321, 330 Boeing 717, 737, 757, 767, 777, 747 MD 88/90

Safety: CPR and First Aid certified and trained in AED

INTERESTS

- Hands Off Atlanta volunteer
- Piedmont Park Conservancy volunteer